

## **SUMMARY**

Worked at Cloudlogic wherein we provide responsive e-commerce website to our top brands client here in the Philippines

Intern at Pierre and Paul Solutions Inc. and Created some applications using Laravel Framework that they are currently using such as PPSI Employee Locator System, Inventory System

## CONTACT

PHONE: 0929-522-5777

WEBSITE PORTFOLIO LINK: https://jndelacruz0420.github.io/jnbdc portfolio/

EMAIL:

Delacruzjohnnoel0922@gmail.com

### **HOBBIES**

Playing online games Watching movies Travel

# JOHN NOEL B. DELA CRUZ

Web Developer

# **EDUCATION**

San Juan National High School

2008 - 2012

P. Narciso St. Brgy. Corazon De Jesus San Juan City

### Polytechnic University of the Philippines

2012 - 2014, 2017 - 2019

Bachelor of Science Information Technology (Graduate)

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Pierre and Paul Solutions Inc. Software Developer (Intern)

Dec 2018 - March 2019

- Developed useful office software application using Laravel 5
- Developed PPSI Empcator and Accounting system

# **Cloudlogic Web Developer**

Apr 2019 - Current

- Developed top brands E-commerce website in the Philippines with responsive design
- Contributed to back-end experience and collaborated on APIs.

# **SKILLS**

- MySQL
- Google Analytics
- iQuery
- Project management
- CSS
- JavaScript
- HTML
- Ajax
- MVC Frameworks